viscoupons.com 2011-12-26

# VisCoupons.com� Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Following is the Privacy Policy of www.viscoupons.com.

Get more information about our terms and conditions at www.viscoupons.com/privacy.htm which came into existence by taking care of the privacy guidelines meant for governing the use of our online and mobile services, any content or information therein, the www.viscoupons.com website and mobile website, any subdomains of viscoupons.com, downloads, and any other website pages on which services are provided by us (collectively, the "Site").

Our privacy policy is developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality offers, coupons and deals for various products and services with integrity while dealing with our users. Our privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding the nature of collection, usage and storage of the personal information provided by the users. Please read the Privacy Policy carefully. Our Privacy Policy can be a subject of regular review and modifications. All modifications will be effective immediately upon posting to the site and you will see the effective date of the latest version of the privacy policy on the website. Therefore, it is entirely your responsibility to regularly check the site to determine the changes pertaining to the **Privacy Policy**. Please contact us via provided email address for further query and comments. 

What Information Do We Collect? 

When you register with us and/or visit the site, you generally provide us with two types of information: Firstly, the information you actively choose to disclose ("Active Information") and secondly, the information collected in an invisible way to you on an aggregate, anonymous basis as you browse the site ("Passive Information"). When we refer to the "personally identifiable information," we mean information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number, or email address. Sharing personally identifiable information with us is entirely optional.

No Use of Our Site by Children Under 13 years!

The Site is not intended to be used by anyone under 13, except with the explicit permission and under the supervision of a parent or guardian who accepts full legal responsibility for the minor's use. No individual under 13 cannot disclose information on this site. We don't collect or use personally identifiable information from children under 13 knowingly. If a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without the consent of the parents or a guardian, they should contact us at the email address provided below to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. You may learn more about protecting children's privacy online. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE.

Active Information You Choose to Provide!

You may choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, in order to register with the site and to receive coupons by SMS, email or other services or information. You may also choose to provide us with your Zip code and city name or other location information to receive information about products and services in your desired area, and you may choose to provide your age, gender, and other information to receive information about products and services which may be of your interest.

Passive Information We Collect!

Our site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how the site is being used. Passive Information gathered by use may include your Internet service provider, browser type, operating system, the date and time of visits, location of your searches, the site pages viewed, time spent at our Site, and the sites visited just before and just after the site. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that your identity remains anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the "Help" section of your browser to correctly do so. If you choose to turn off the cookies, however, and/or if you elect not to share certain information with us, you may not be able to access certain features of the Site and your use of some portions of the site may be affected.

What is a Cookie?

Cookies are a web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.) feature software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are really small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies make your online experience easier and more personalized.

How Do We Use the Information Collected?

**Active Information**

The Active Information provided by you help us in delivering the content, features, advertising, services, or the information requested. If you provide us with your email address, we will send you the information or other messages related to your activities on the site or about our services. We may retain the Active Information you provide and a record of the service or information provided. Any Active Information retained would be used to assist the delivery of the content, features, advertising, services, or information and to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online. We may use the Active Information provided by users about the changes in the site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you will find valuable. In case you wish to dis-continue receiving such information, please send us an email at privacy@viscoupons.com. When you send us a message, we retain the content of the message, your email address and any information you may provide to us, including your experience with the site, and your contact preferences as well as the response we send back to you. This helps us to manage any follow-up questions you may have, measure how effectively we address your concerns, and improve the Site. 

We may share or permit access to Active Information with persons we employ directly or as contractors or agents, partners, or affiliates at our direction, for purposes of administering our business activities, processing information, fulfilling coupon requests, providing marketing assistance, providing customer services such as support, and making available other product or service offers or deals we think may be of interest to you. If we are acquired by another company, your personally identifiable information will be shared with our new owner, but it will remain a subject to the terms of then-applicable privacy policy.

Passive Information

We use Passive Information to enhance and design our site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use, and to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online. Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit the site, when they visit and how they use our services. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis and we do not connect any of this information to your email address or other personally identifiable information. However, Passive Information may result in your viewing of particular content, features, advertising, services, or information based on your user habits or your viewing on the site.

Your Information and Links to Other Web Sites

This site contains links to other websites not owned by us that may have different privacy practices from ours. We aren't responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and our Privacy Policy doesn't apply to information collected by those sites. You should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you choose to visit or shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases.

Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties

We may share information with third parties, such as advertisers on our site or other business partners, anonymous, aggregated Active and Passive information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns. We may use your IP address, your browser software (i.e. Internet Explorer, etc.), the configuration used, the pages served, the time, source of a request or other information and share them with third parties to help diagnose problems with our servers, to manage the Site, to analyze trends and to enhance the Site based on usage pattern data. Third party advertisers may match this information with that which they have previously collected about you under their own privacy policies, which you should consult on a regular basis.

We may combine the Passive information and anonymous non-personally identifiable Active Information with demographic information about users that we receive from our marketing or other partners, and sell such aggregated and/or trend data to third parties.

Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law

We may also use or disclose Active and Passive information to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access information when we believe in good faith that the law, court order, subpoena, warrant or administrative agency requires it, or if we consider it necessary to maintain service and improve our products and services. We may also disclose any such information that we believe in good faith is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability, to protect users from fraudulent, abusive or unlawful uses, to investigate and defend any third party claims, to protect the security or integrity of the Site, and to protect the rights, property or safety of viscoupons.com, its affiliates, partners, agents, users or others.

Protection of your Personally Identifiable Information

In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information or Passive Information, we use reasonable efforts to secure the information associated with you. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information, we can't be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, AND WE MAKE NO WARRANTY, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR OTHERWISE, THAT WE WILL PREVENT SUCH ACCESS OR THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL NOT BE DISCLOSED, ALTERED OR DESTROYED BY A BREACH OF OUR PHYSICAL, TECHNICAL OR MANAGERIAL SAFEGUARDS Communications you may have with us via email or U.S. Mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR PASSWORDS AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION.

Contests and Promotions

If you choose to enter any contest, sweepstakes or other promotion offered on this Site, your personally identifiable information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion.

Public Access

Please note that if you directly disclose personal information in a bulletin board, chat room, forum, or any other public area of the Site (if any), such information is not subject to this Privacy Policy and may be collected and used by others, and you may receive unsolicited messages from third parties.

Changes

You should review this Privacy Policy whenever you access or operate the Site in order to be aware of the ways that your information is used. We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy at any time. If you do not accept such changes, you must discontinue the Site. Any such change will apply to information or other materials that you provide us on or after the effective date of the change. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE AFTER SUCH CHANGES SHALL CONSTITUTE YOUR ACCEPTANCE TO SUCH CHANGES. This Privacy Policy is effective 1 March 2011.This Privacy Policy was last modified 7 March 2011.

International Users

This Site is hosted and operated in India. Those who access or use the Site from other jurisdictions do so at their own choice and risk and are solely responsible for compliance with local law. Please note that the personal information you submit to our Site will be transferred to and stored in the India to be processed by us so we can provide this Site to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy .

If you are not a resident of India, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personal information outside your home jurisdiction, and that we may store your personal information in India. 

Contacting Mobilecoupons.com about Your Information or Information You Receive

If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you wish to access, delete or correct your information, please send us an email to privacy@viscoupons.com

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use or disclosure of your personally identifiable information, please write to us at:

Privacy@viscoupons.com 

C-15, Sector-3

Noida, 201301

Uttar Pradesh, India
